{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Outbuilding \u0026 Shelter Builders","__cache./api/resource/task/40346/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40346,"taskName":"Shelter or Outbuilding - Build","taskDescription":"Construct a Shelter or Below Ground Outbuilding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Outbuilding \u0026 Shelter Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":235,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Shelter enclosure out free addition","textMessagingName":"Shelter/Outbuilding","rolloverLongDesc":"Can be custom built or fully pre-fab units that come all complete on a truck. Underground buildings \u0026 shelter are usually used for their durability \u0026 security \u0026 sometimes invisibility.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes storm, survival \u0026 bomb shelters.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Construct a Shelter or Below Ground Outbuilding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Build a Shelter (Storm, Tornado) \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Outbuilding Construction","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Shelter or Outbuilding Build","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Shelter or Outbuilding - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outbuilding or Shelter Project","urlName":"Shelter-or-Outbuilding-Build","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Shelter Builders (Storm, Tornado) - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Shelter,enclosure,out,free,addition,storage,steel,metal,building,freestanding,Outbuilding,Build","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":640,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40346/":{"taskOID":40346,"originalTaskOID":40346,"setID":640,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4636,"questionDisplayText":"Number of People to use Shelter","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many people will the shelter protect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":488,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4-6 people","answerDisplayText":"4-6 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":547,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-8 people","answerDisplayText":"6-8 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10 people","answerDisplayText":"8-10 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4637,"questionDisplayText":"Shelter Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material would you like the shelter made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4638,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the shelter be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6585,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Underground in yard","answerDisplayText":"Underground in yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6583,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Under foundation before new construction","answerDisplayText":"Under foundation before new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2112,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dug out under existing home","answerDisplayText":"Dug out under existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4639,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want in your shelter?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","answerDisplayText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1192,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","answerDisplayText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second emergency door","answerDisplayText":"Second emergency door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","answerDisplayText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6908,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water storage tank","answerDisplayText":"Water storage tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1367,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Chemical toilet","answerDisplayText":"Chemical toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Weatherband radio","answerDisplayText":"Weatherband radio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7029,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","answerDisplayText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2463,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fire safe","answerDisplayText":"Fire safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4538,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Padded seats or benches","answerDisplayText":"Padded seats or benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1249,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Carpet","answerDisplayText":"Carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4636,"questionDisplayText":"Number of People to use Shelter","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many people will the shelter protect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":488,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4-6 people","answerDisplayText":"4-6 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":547,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-8 people","answerDisplayText":"6-8 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10 people","answerDisplayText":"8-10 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":488,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4-6 people","answerDisplayText":"4-6 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":547,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-8 people","answerDisplayText":"6-8 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":563,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10 people","answerDisplayText":"8-10 people","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4637,"questionDisplayText":"Shelter Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material would you like the shelter made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4638,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the shelter be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6585,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Underground in yard","answerDisplayText":"Underground in yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6583,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Under foundation before new construction","answerDisplayText":"Under foundation before new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2112,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dug out under existing home","answerDisplayText":"Dug out under existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6585,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Underground in yard","answerDisplayText":"Underground in yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6583,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Under foundation before new construction","answerDisplayText":"Under foundation before new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2112,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dug out under existing home","answerDisplayText":"Dug out under existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4639,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want in your shelter?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","answerDisplayText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1192,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","answerDisplayText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second emergency door","answerDisplayText":"Second emergency door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","answerDisplayText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6908,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water storage tank","answerDisplayText":"Water storage tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1367,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Chemical toilet","answerDisplayText":"Chemical toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Weatherband radio","answerDisplayText":"Weatherband radio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7029,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","answerDisplayText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2463,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fire safe","answerDisplayText":"Fire safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4538,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Padded seats or benches","answerDisplayText":"Padded seats or benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1249,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Carpet","answerDisplayText":"Carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","answerDisplayText":"Rechargeable battery-operated lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1192,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","answerDisplayText":"Bunk beds and mattresses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second emergency door","answerDisplayText":"Second emergency door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","answerDisplayText":"Hydraulic jack to open door if obstructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6908,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water storage tank","answerDisplayText":"Water storage tank","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1367,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Chemical toilet","answerDisplayText":"Chemical toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Weatherband radio","answerDisplayText":"Weatherband radio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7029,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","answerDisplayText":"Wired for electricity, phone lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2463,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fire safe","answerDisplayText":"Fire safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4538,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Padded seats or benches","answerDisplayText":"Padded seats or benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1249,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Carpet","answerDisplayText":"Carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}